1
00:00:19,482 --> 00:00:21,484
那 呃 还有谁是确定了的
Selina: And, uh, who else is confirmed?

2
00:00:21,585 --> 00:00:23,686
Dorsey参议员确定了吗
Is senator Dorsey confirmed?

3
00:00:23,687 --> 00:00:25,020
是的 - 好
Yes. - Okay.

4
00:00:25,021 --> 00:00:26,656
本来Lucas参议员还是未知数
And senator Lucas was a maybe,

5
00:00:26,657 --> 00:00:28,526
但现在肯定会来
but now he's definitely a definitely.

6
00:00:28,527 --> 00:00:31,162
噢 那太好了 - 是啊 发表演说后支持者不断上升
- Oh, that's awfully nice. - Yeah, it's growing as we speak.

7
00:00:31,163 --> 00:00:33,198
很好 去探讨冗长辩论改革问题吧
Yeah, okay, let's go talk filibuster reform.

8
00:00:33,199 --> 00:00:36,801
不行 副总统今天日程已经满了
No, the Vice President does not have a sliver of daylight in her schedule today.

9
00:00:36,802 --> 00:00:38,803
再见 Sue 嘿 Mike Mike - 怎么了
- Bye, Sue. Hey, Mike, Mike. - Yeah?

10
00:00:38,804 --> 00:00:41,272
玉米淀粉餐具活动进展如何
Are we pushing the whole Cornstarch Utensils campaign now?

11
00:00:41,273 --> 00:00:42,941
是的 女士 一切都在线运作
Yes, ma'am. We've got a whole online thing.

12
00:00:42,942 --> 00:00:44,477
各种全面运转 - 嗯 很好
- The inter-nerds are on it. - Okay, good.

13
00:00:44,478 --> 00:00:46,812
见到参议员们后 记得微笑
And today with the senators, don't forget to smile.

14
00:00:46,813 --> 00:00:49,081
好 你牙上的是罂粟子吗
Yeah, is that a poppy seed there in your teeth?

15
00:00:49,082 --> 00:00:51,683
有可能 - 嗯 恶
- Oh, probably. - Yeah, ugh.

16
00:00:51,684 --> 00:00:52,951
噢 - 什么
- Oh! - What?

17
00:00:52,952 --> 00:00:55,286
Bixby参议员会来 - 噢 真好
- Senator Bixby is coming. - Oh, good.

18
00:00:55,287 --> 00:00:57,155
太好了 - 女士 这是个叉子
- Great. - Ma'am, this is a fork.

19
00:00:57,156 --> 00:00:59,624
要记住他是我们的导游 - 他是导游
- And you know that he's our tour guide. - He's the tour guide.

20
00:00:59,625 --> 00:01:01,059
对 是的 是的 - 记得吧?
- Right, yes, yes, yes. - Remember?

21
00:01:01,060 --> 00:01:02,728
这是最新的玉米淀粉叉子 女士
This is the new Cornstarch fork, ma'am.

22
00:01:02,729 --> 00:01:04,631
还有玉米淀粉汤匙
I got the Cornstarch spoon, too.

23
00:01:04,632 --> 00:01:06,232
我们能不能把餐具放一放 Gary
Could we maybe table tableware for now, Gary,

24
00:01:06,233 --> 00:01:08,868
先搞定冗长辩论改革 - 不不不 Amy 看
- and focus on filibuster reform? - No, no, no, but, Amy, look.

25
00:01:08,869 --> 00:01:11,070
看看它 清洁工作必备
Look at this. This is classic clean jobs stuff.

26
00:01:11,071 --> 00:01:13,072
如果入秋之前我能让它
I mean, if I can get Cornstarch Utensils

27
00:01:13,073 --> 00:01:14,807
入驻大部分联邦政府大楼
in most federal buildings by the fall,

28
00:01:14,808 --> 00:01:17,009
副总统的宝座就坐稳了
well, then the VEEP has landed.

29
00:01:17,010 --> 00:01:18,644
这也是我们想做的 助您稳居宝座
That is what we are working on, landing you.

30
00:01:18,645 --> 00:01:21,014
当然 - 就像只又大又漂亮的老鹰
- Yeah. - Like a big, beautiful eagle.

31
00:01:23,617 --> 00:01:25,385
戴围巾吗 - 不戴
you want your scarf? - No.

32
00:01:25,386 --> 00:01:26,752
你确定? 这个很漂亮... - 我不想戴
- Are you sure? It looks really pretty... - No, I don't want it.

33
00:01:26,753 --> 00:01:29,922
Reeves参议员怎么样了 死了没
And what about senator Reeves? Is he dead yet?

34
00:01:29,923 --> 00:01:32,391
还没 他现在主要靠静脉注射
Not yet. He's mostly intravenous.

35
00:01:32,392 --> 00:01:35,460
身上插满了管子 就像风笛一样
He has so many tubes in him, he looks like a set of bagpipes.

36
00:01:38,598 --> 00:01:40,332
我帮你拿外套 - 外套不拿了吧?
Let me take your coat. - want to take your coats?

37
00:01:40,333 --> 00:01:43,036
您的眼镜 - 你觉得怎样
- Here's your glasses. - What do you think?

38
00:01:43,037 --> 00:01:45,471
戴眼镜的知识女性形象?
Glasses on for the intellectual look?

39
00:01:45,472 --> 00:01:47,975
专注力? - 有远见的女人
Focused? - a woman with vision.

40
00:01:47,976 --> 00:01:50,478
您戴眼镜很好看 - 不行 眼镜会削弱我的气势
- I like your glasses. - No, glasses make me look weak.

41
00:01:50,479 --> 00:01:53,748
嗯 我同意 - 就像是给眼睛的轮椅一样
- Yeah, I agree. - It's like a wheelchair for the eye.

42
00:01:53,749 --> 00:01:56,951
好了 参议员们 改革开始吧
Okay, senators, let the reforming commence.

43
00:01:56,952 --> 00:01:59,154
希望有50到60 - 噢 好
- Amy: We're expecting 50 or 60. - Oh, good.

44
00:02:01,791 --> 00:02:05,161
是这个房间吗 我们是不是来早了
Is this the right room? Are we early?

45
00:02:05,162 --> 00:02:07,397
Phil Dorsey参议员 两点钟方向 - 我又不是狙击手
- Senator Phil Dorsey, 2:00. - I'm not a sniper.

46
00:02:07,398 --> 00:02:10,166
Philip - 副总统女士 欢迎
- Philip. - Ah, Madam Vice President. Welcome.

47
00:02:10,167 --> 00:02:12,641
谢谢 还记得我的幕僚长Amy吧 - Amy
Thank you. Oh, you remember my chief of staff Amy.

48
00:02:12,642 --> 00:02:13,907
很高兴见到你
Oh, Amy. It's nice to see you.

49
00:02:13,908 --> 00:02:15,472
他女儿Emily刚从哈佛毕业
His daughter Emily just graduated from Harvard.

50
00:02:15,473 --> 00:02:18,209
告诉我 Emily还好吗 - 噢 她很好
- Tell me, how is Emily? - Oh, she's good.

51
00:02:18,210 --> 00:02:20,211
真好 - 要喝什么吗
- Oh, good. - Can I get you something to drink?

52
00:02:20,212 --> 00:02:22,079
有咖啡最好了 - 马上来
- I would love a coffee. - You've got it.

53
00:02:22,080 --> 00:02:24,782
谢谢 为什么会这样 Amy
Okay, thank you. What's going on, Amy?

54
00:02:24,783 --> 00:02:26,951
这人数连他妈的独木舟都填不满
There aren't enough people to fill a fucking canoe in here.

55
00:02:26,952 --> 00:02:30,355
怎么这样 - 怎么了 这是你的问题好吧
- Okay. - What's wrong? That was your bad okay.

56
00:02:30,356 --> 00:02:33,759
怎么了 Mike Dudley参议员 喜欢地图
What's wrong? Senator Mike Dudley. He's interested in maps.

57
00:02:33,760 --> 00:02:36,862
Mike 你找到我们了 - 噢 副总统女士
- Mike, you found us. - Oh, Madam Vice President.

58
00:02:36,863 --> 00:02:39,264
这是个地图笑话吗 - 是的
- Is that a map joke? - Yes, it is.

59
00:02:39,265 --> 00:02:41,233
不好意思 走开一下
Oh, sorry. Excuse me.

60
00:02:41,234 --> 00:02:43,335
好 - 我们来说说这个博客
- Okay. - Let's talk about this blog thing.

61
00:02:43,336 --> 00:02:45,270
伙计们 这是怎么回事 - 我可以解释
- Guys, what's going on right now? - I can explain that.

62
00:02:45,271 --> 00:02:46,772
现在是什么情况
What is happening right now?

63
00:02:46,773 --> 00:02:49,007
Brett Kagan的博文引用了我们的围脖
Brett Kagan's blog picked up a tweet from us.

64
00:02:49,008 --> 00:02:51,076
上面说76%政府大楼
Quote, 76% of government buildings

65
00:02:51,077 --> 00:02:54,079
都在用玉米淀粉餐具 我们要做到百分之百
now have Cornstarch Utensils! Let's make it 100!

66
00:02:54,080 --> 00:02:56,147
杜绝塑料餐具
Let's make plastic utensils extinct!

67
00:02:56,148 --> 00:02:59,217
太好了 我们得罪了塑料行业
Oh, great, we've upset the plastics industry.

68
00:02:59,218 --> 00:03:01,953
这整栋楼都是塑料行业赞助的
This whole building is bankrolled by plastics.

69
00:03:01,954 --> 00:03:04,189
所以他们才不来 - 副总统女士
- This is why nobody showed up. - Man: Madam Vice President.

70
00:03:04,190 --> 00:03:06,758
我不知道他是谁 - 你好
- I don't know who this man is. - Hello.

71
00:03:06,759 --> 00:03:08,394
Mike 说话 我现在这个房间只有三个人
Mike, talk to me. I am in a room

72
00:03:08,395 --> 00:03:10,563
还有他妈一堆乳蛋饼
with three people and a fuckload of quiche.

73
00:03:10,564 --> 00:03:11,964
Dorsey参议员拿着咖啡来了
Okay, here comes Dorsey with your coffee.

74
00:03:11,965 --> 00:03:14,334
Gary 全场我都能看到
Gary, I have large, moving shapes covered.

75
00:03:14,335 --> 00:03:15,802
好 - 知道吧?
Okay. Okay. - Okay?

76
00:03:15,803 --> 00:03:19,039
您的咖啡 - 噢 我的咖...
- Here's your coffee. - Oh, my co...

77
00:03:19,040 --> 00:03:21,408
我去拿 我能搞定
I'll get it. I got it. I got it.

78
00:03:21,409 --> 00:03:23,243
好 我们有对策了
Okay, here's what we do. Here's what we do.

79
00:03:23,244 --> 00:03:24,845
你要去找Hallowes参议员
You should meet with senator Hallowes.

80
00:03:24,846 --> 00:03:27,480
她跟塑料行业的人联系非常紧密...
She is stight with the plastics people, it's...

81
00:03:27,481 --> 00:03:29,515
你在玩我吗
Are you kidding?

82
00:03:29,516 --> 00:03:31,784
这些敢不敢不弯成这样
Do these not bend the fuck back?

83
00:03:31,785 --> 00:03:33,752
可以 可以
No. No.

84
00:03:33,753 --> 00:03:34,887
我要拿这个干什么
What am I supposed to do with this?

85
00:03:34,888 --> 00:03:36,488
我拿着它到处晃
I'm supposed to eat around corners?

86
00:03:36,489 --> 00:03:38,624
你是这么准备的吗 拿走 麻烦你
Is that how's gonna work? Here, take this, please.

87
00:03:38,625 --> 00:03:42,095
我们可以为Hallowes 在清洁工作委员会安排位置
We could even give Hallowes a post on your clean jobs commission,

88
00:03:42,096 --> 00:03:44,130
讨好塑料业 - 这个主意不错
- keep plastics happy. - That's actually a great idea.

89
00:03:44,131 --> 00:03:47,033
你可以做到吗 现在联系Hallowes?
Can you do that? Can you do that? Can you get Hallowes now?

90
00:03:47,034 --> 00:03:49,303
当然可以 你可以直接结束这里
Of course I can. You can just shut it down.

91
00:03:49,304 --> 00:03:51,105
好 去 去 - 直接结束
- Yeah. Go, go, go. - Shut it down.

92
00:03:51,106 --> 00:03:53,108
你得去周旋 - 周旋?
you should mingle. - Mingle?

93
00:03:53,109 --> 00:03:54,576
是 - 什么
Yeah. - What?

94
00:03:54,577 --> 00:03:56,845
这么点儿人你让我怎么周旋
How do you suggest that I mingle with this few people?

95
00:03:56,846 --> 00:03:59,948
Simon会跟Garfunkel周旋吗 (Simon&Garfunkel 著名二人乐队)
Did Simon mingle with Garfunkel?

96
00:03:59,949 --> 00:04:02,384
他们一起工作 可能也会一起交际
Well, they work together. They probably socialized together.

97
00:04:02,385 --> 00:04:03,853
我觉得他们会的 对不
I'm sure they did, right?

98
00:04:03,854 --> 00:04:06,789
副总统女士 嗨 我是Dan Egan
Madam Vice President. Hi, I'm Dan Egan.

99
00:04:06,790 --> 00:04:08,591
我是Hallowes参议员的公关经理
I'm director of communications for senator Hallowes.

100
00:04:08,592 --> 00:04:10,059
噢 好 - 现任的
- Oh, good. - Currently.

101
00:04:10,060 --> 00:04:11,928
我特别支持
I just want to say that I'm a huge fan

102
00:04:11,929 --> 00:04:13,663
您的清洁工作计划 - 谢谢
- of the clean jobs initiative. - Oh, thank you.

103
00:04:13,664 --> 00:04:16,232
我说过的 这是个肮脏活儿 可我就是喜欢
Well, you know what I say, it's a dirty job and I love to do it.

104
00:04:16,233 --> 00:04:18,334
哈 很好笑 实际我...
- Ha, that's funny. I actually... - Barbara?

105
00:04:18,335 --> 00:04:21,371
Selina 嗨 - 嗨
- Selina, hi. - Hi.

106
00:04:21,372 --> 00:04:24,240
这是副总统 她通过...
The Vice President, or VEEP, has managed to punch her way through...

107
00:04:24,241 --> 00:04:26,041
谢谢 Dan
Thank you, Dan. Yeah.

108
00:04:26,042 --> 00:04:27,776
Barbara 见到你太好了
Barbara, it's so good to see you.

109
00:04:27,777 --> 00:04:30,078
很高兴见到你 - 我刚错过了什么吗
- It's good to see you. - What have I been missing here?

110
00:04:30,079 --> 00:04:32,881
权力 开玩笑的
Power. I'm kidding!

111
00:04:32,882 --> 00:04:35,450
噢 Selina - 了解 了解
- Oh, Selina. - I know. I know.

112
00:04:35,451 --> 00:04:37,285
请给副总统上杯咖啡 Dan
Coffee for the Vice President, please, Dan.

113
00:04:37,286 --> 00:04:39,387
你猜怎么着 我要去找
Guess what? I've managed to get a fresh batch

114
00:04:39,388 --> 00:04:41,056
你最喜欢的欧洲产糖精
of those European sweeners you like so much.

115
00:04:41,057 --> 00:04:43,758
谢谢 Gary 那个糖精很好
Oh, thanks, Gary. Yeah, they're great sweeteners.

116
00:04:43,759 --> 00:04:45,927
好难吃
They are awful.

117
00:04:45,928 --> 00:04:50,132
其实就是去年我开个北约会议时搞到的
Actually, they're just sweeteners I got at a NATO meeting last year.

118
00:04:50,133 --> 00:04:53,769
它们味道有点...
They really taste rather...

119
00:04:54,938 --> 00:04:58,308
呃 不好
Uh, unpleasant.

120
00:04:58,309 --> 00:04:59,576
有点苦
Kind of bitter.

121
00:04:59,577 --> 00:05:02,612
Dan 你为Hallowes工作顺利吗
So, Dan, are you enjoying working for Hallowes?

122
00:05:02,613 --> 00:05:05,215
不咋地 她就是中等
Not really. She's middle of the road.

123
00:05:05,216 --> 00:05:08,418
不好不坏 在平庸里面算是中间的
She's mediocre, really. Of all the -ocres, she's the mediest.

124
00:05:08,419 --> 00:05:11,522
我往里面加水了吗 这就像个机器人
Do I add water to this machine? It's like a bot.

125
00:05:11,523 --> 00:05:14,626
包不错 Gary
It's a nice bag, Gary.

126
00:05:14,627 --> 00:05:16,594
他叫它利维坦
You know, he calls that The Leviathan.

127
00:05:16,595 --> 00:05:19,064
呵 你往里面放了核电码吗 哥们
Ooh, you got the nuclear codes in there, buddy?

128
00:05:19,065 --> 00:05:21,866
我要不要往里面放个小袋还是什么
Is there a pouch or something that I put into this?

129
00:05:21,867 --> 00:05:24,870
你们还是让Mike做新闻吗
You still got that guy Mike in your press shop?

130
00:05:24,871 --> 00:05:26,806
是 - 他以前帮Moses做新闻的 是不是
- Yes. - He ran press for Moses, didn't he?

131
00:05:26,807 --> 00:05:29,475
天呐 - 你这没有浓缩咖啡什么的吗
- Oh, God. - Is there like an espresso thing?

132
00:05:29,476 --> 00:05:32,145
那种一小袋的 - 妈的受不了了
a little podule or anything? - Jesus fucking Christ.

133
00:05:32,146 --> 00:05:34,415
看我做 自闭君 拿些咖啡豆
All right, look, watch me, autismo. You take the little pod,

134
00:05:34,416 --> 00:05:36,584
放进狗日的洞 关上狗日的盖子
put the little pod in the fucking hole, shut the fucking lid,

135
00:05:36,585 --> 00:05:38,652
按他妈两秒钟开关
hit the fucking button for two fucking seconds.

136
00:05:38,653 --> 00:05:41,254
噢 好简单哦亲 - 太快了 没看到
- Oh, it's so easy. - Too quick, I didn't see it.

137
00:05:41,255 --> 00:05:43,824
那下次记得在你的操蛋的包里带个浓缩咖啡机
Yeah, well, next time pack an espresso machine in your big fuckin' bitch bag.

138
00:05:43,825 --> 00:05:45,825
天呐 Dan好像人不错
- Oh, my God. - Dan seems nice.

139
00:05:45,826 --> 00:05:47,493
他是新来的 - 他很棒
- He's new. - Oh, he is great.

140
00:05:47,494 --> 00:05:50,296
很忠诚 我从一个俄亥俄女参议员那聘来的
Very loyal. I got him from an Ohio congresswoman.

141
00:05:50,297 --> 00:05:52,931
他在和我女儿恋爱
You know, he's dating my daughter.

142
00:05:52,932 --> 00:05:55,267
真的假的 Janet? - 不是
- You're kidding. Janet? - No.

143
00:05:55,268 --> 00:05:57,502
肯定不是 天呐 对不起
Of course not. Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry.

144
00:05:57,503 --> 00:06:00,038
我是说 呃 Carol
I meant, um, Carol.

145
00:06:00,039 --> 00:06:01,706
Carol.

146
00:06:01,707 --> 00:06:04,875
孩子们怎么样 - 嗯 她很好
- How are your kids? - Uh, she's good.

147
00:06:06,278 --> 00:06:08,446
我知道你很忙 - 非常忙
- I understand you're busy. - I am.

148
00:06:08,447 --> 00:06:11,248
不过我想跟你谈谈
But I wanted to talk to you about

149
00:06:11,249 --> 00:06:13,651
即将出台的清洁工作委员会
coming on board the clean jobs commission.

150
00:06:13,652 --> 00:06:15,654
要塑料行业不再嘲弄你?
To get plastics off your back?

151
00:06:15,655 --> 00:06:17,589
不行 对不起 Selina 这样我很难做
No, sorry, Selina. That would be bad for me.

152
00:06:17,590 --> 00:06:21,960
拜托 他们不会因为这个撤资的
Oh, come on. They're not gonna pull funding over this.

153
00:06:21,961 --> 00:06:23,828
甜心 塑料是什么做的
Honey, what is plastics made of?

154
00:06:23,829 --> 00:06:25,964
你得罪塑料业就是得罪石油业
You piss off plastics, you piss off oil.

155
00:06:25,965 --> 00:06:27,265
你不会想开罪他们的
And you do not want to fuck with those guys

156
00:06:27,266 --> 00:06:30,268
因为后果很严重
because they fuck in a very unpleasant fashion.

157
00:06:30,269 --> 00:06:34,139
Barbara 你真的愿意出卖自己人格吗
Barbara, are you really willing to sell your soul

158
00:06:34,140 --> 00:06:35,740
就为了这些做牙刷的
to the guys who make toothbrushes

159
00:06:35,741 --> 00:06:37,075
还...还...
and... and... and... and...

160
00:06:37,076 --> 00:06:39,912
还有牙刷柄的
and the holders for toothbrushes?

161
00:06:39,913 --> 00:06:42,147
对 他们还资助了
Yeah, they're the guys who fund the members

162
00:06:42,148 --> 00:06:44,116
你的清洁工作委员会成员
of your clean jobs commission.

163
00:06:44,117 --> 00:06:47,853
我可以给你画个表 不过肯定会画得很简单的
I could draw you a diagram, but it would be a very simple diagram.

164
00:06:47,854 --> 00:06:50,189
我看得懂几何 好吧 Barbara
Oh, I can handle geometry, Barbara, all right?

165
00:06:50,190 --> 00:06:52,691
好了 我要走了 - 当然 我也有...
- Come on, I've got to get going. - Yes, well, I have...

166
00:06:52,692 --> 00:06:55,394
很多日程
a ton on my agenda as well.

167
00:06:55,395 --> 00:06:58,798
刚有消息 Reeves参议员刚过世了
Watch this. Uh, senator Reeves just died.

168
00:06:58,799 --> 00:07:00,366
噢
Oh.

169
00:07:00,367 --> 00:07:02,935
Oh. - Rapey Reeves.

170
00:07:02,936 --> 00:07:06,405
他是第一个欢迎我进国会的参议员 知道吗
He was the first senator to welcome me to the Capitol, you know?

171
00:07:06,406 --> 00:07:08,006
那时他就很老了
He was old even then.

172
00:07:08,007 --> 00:07:10,976
他是不是充满了智慧? - 他充满了酒气
Was he full of wisdom? - he Was full of bourbon.

173
00:07:10,977 --> 00:07:13,011
他还抓了我左边乳房
And he grabbed my left tit.

174
00:07:13,012 --> 00:07:15,046
记得吧 - 愿他安息
Remember that? - And God rest his soul.

175
00:07:15,047 --> 00:07:18,383
嘿 你炒了那个写博客的没
Hey, did you fire your tweet monkey yet?

176
00:07:18,384 --> 00:07:21,587
他就是个武器级的绊脚石
Because that guy is a weapons-grade retard.

177
00:07:21,588 --> 00:07:24,189
我觉得你已经被自己的绊脚石绊住了
I think you might have been hoist by your own retard there.

178
00:07:24,190 --> 00:07:25,858
很不错
That's a good one.

179
00:07:25,859 --> 00:07:27,092
自己的绊脚石 不错
Your own retard. Nice.

180
00:07:27,093 --> 00:07:28,695
楼下见 - 是
- See you downstairs. - Yeah.

181
00:07:28,696 --> 00:07:30,863
很荣幸见到你 女士 - 谢谢 Dan
- Honor to have met you, madam. - Oh, thank you, Dan.

182
00:07:30,864 --> 00:07:32,966
你初选的时候太棒了
I really admired your primaries campaign.

183
00:07:32,967 --> 00:07:34,601
噢 真好 谢谢你
Oh, how nice. Thank you very much.

184
00:07:34,602 --> 00:07:36,103
两处有待改善
Two things I would have done differently.

185
00:07:36,104 --> 00:07:38,905
两处? 真的假的 哪两处
Two things? Oh, no kidding. What were they?

186
00:07:38,906 --> 00:07:41,341
你在新罕布什尔上耗太久 本来就是囊中物
I think you spent too much time in new Hampshire. That was in the bag.

187
00:07:41,342 --> 00:07:43,610
俄勒冈的攻击广告早出了四天
And the attack ads in Oregon came up four days too soon,

188
00:07:43,611 --> 00:07:45,312
不该刻薄的时候刻薄了
made you seem mean before you had to be.

189
00:07:45,313 --> 00:07:47,580
不过 你还是占上风的
But, I mean, hey, you're the old pro here.

190
00:07:47,581 --> 00:07:49,215
你胜算还大
- Gary: Ooh! - You're the pro.

191
00:07:49,216 --> 00:07:51,684
我会记住的
Well, I'll keep that in mind.

192
00:07:54,454 --> 00:07:56,021
参议员会议的事我很遗憾
Mike: Sorry about the Senate meeting.

193
00:07:56,022 --> 00:07:59,358
那就像是为无家可归的人准备的葬礼
Yeah, it was like a funeral for a homeless guy.

194
00:07:59,359 --> 00:08:01,727
Hallowes怎么样 - 就跟平常一样
- How was Hallowes? - Oh, you know, the usual.

195
00:08:01,728 --> 00:08:03,928
Selina 嗨
Selina, hi.

196
00:08:03,929 --> 00:08:06,765
我在融化 我在融化
I'm melting. I'm melting.

197
00:08:06,766 --> 00:08:08,400
她就是个婊子
She is such a fucking bitch.

198
00:08:08,401 --> 00:08:11,303
今天3:30的记者致电
So today at the 3:30 press call,

199
00:08:11,304 --> 00:08:12,738
对于塑料产业的事 你想我怎么回应
what do you want me to say about plastics?

200
00:08:12,739 --> 00:08:16,008
我觉得最好是能安抚... - 哇哦
I think our best agenda is to reassure... - Whoa.

201
00:08:16,009 --> 00:08:17,776
我知道 不要告诉我 - 什么
- I know. Don't tell me. - What?

202
00:08:17,777 --> 00:08:20,846
如果我是真不知道 那群混蛋也不能 从我嘴里套到什么
If I genuinely don't know, then those bastards can't make me tell them.

203
00:08:20,847 --> 00:08:22,915
你知道我的座右铭 我不想知道
You know my motto, I don't want to know.

204
00:08:22,916 --> 00:08:25,084
要是有问座右铭是什么 我就说没有
Anyways, what motto? I don't have a motto.

205
00:08:26,186 --> 00:08:28,555
嘿 Sue 总统打了电话没
Hey, Sue. Did the president call?

206
00:08:28,556 --> 00:08:30,257
没有 - 没有
No. - No.

207
00:08:30,258 --> 00:08:31,826
嘿 Sue 裙子真好看
Hey, Sue, that is a lovely dress.

208
00:08:31,827 --> 00:08:33,594
谢谢 Gary 副总统女士 - 怎么
- Thank you, Gary. Madam Vice President. - Yeah?

209
00:08:33,595 --> 00:08:35,330
我们要重新同步您的手机
We're gonna need to resync your BlackBerry.

210
00:08:35,331 --> 00:08:37,265
好 - 那些日志被动手脚了
- Okay. - The diary's been violated.

211
00:08:37,266 --> 00:08:38,934
女士 您的咖啡 很烫
Ma'am, here's your coffee. It's really hot.

212
00:08:38,935 --> 00:08:40,268
可以就放在那儿吗
Can you put it down right there?

213
00:08:40,269 --> 00:08:42,404
噢 Gary 呃...
Oh, Gary. Um...

214
00:08:44,607 --> 00:08:47,476
噢 天呐 我刚想说什么来着
Oh. Oh, my God, what was I just gonna say?

215
00:08:49,279 --> 00:08:51,781
Oh.

216
00:08:51,782 --> 00:08:54,417
不知道 一下子想不起来了
I don't know. It just went out of my head.

217
00:08:54,418 --> 00:08:55,685
待会再说 - 好
- It'll come to me later. - Okay.

218
00:08:55,686 --> 00:08:57,753
白宫的Jonah过来了
And Jonah is here from the White House.

219
00:08:57,754 --> 00:08:59,588
我告诉他你没空
I told him you were too busy to see him,

220
00:08:59,589 --> 00:09:02,157
但是 如你所见 他无视我了 连带你一起
but, as you see, he ignored me and, by implication, you.

221
00:09:02,158 --> 00:09:03,725
嗨 - 噢 副总统女士
- Hi. - Oh, Madam Vice President.

222
00:09:03,726 --> 00:09:06,528
关门 边出边关 快点 快点
Close the door. On your way out, close it. Quickly. Quick, quick.

223
00:09:06,529 --> 00:09:08,062
快 快 万能的主啊
Quick, quick. God Almighty.

224
00:09:08,063 --> 00:09:09,730
不行
No.

225
00:09:09,731 --> 00:09:11,398
你看了维基百科没
You, did you check the Wikipedia?

226
00:09:11,399 --> 00:09:12,966
他们又改了她体重吗
Did they change her weight again?

227
00:09:12,967 --> 00:09:15,502
老是有人入侵系统改她的体重
Somebody keeps hacking into the site and changing her weight.

228
00:09:15,503 --> 00:09:17,170
噢 Jonah
Oh, Jonah.

229
00:09:17,171 --> 00:09:19,939
市区有家不错的意大利餐厅开业了 Amy
Good new Italian place opened up downtown, Amy.

230
00:09:19,940 --> 00:09:22,676
喜欢意大利菜吗 - 超级爱 Jonah
- You like Italian? - I love Italian, Jonah,

231
00:09:22,677 --> 00:09:24,877
不幸的是 我还是一如既往嫌弃你
but still, unfortunately, really dislike you.

232
00:09:24,878 --> 00:09:27,780
我没有要约你出去 我也不想你因为
Oh, I wasn't asking you out. I don't want you to think

233
00:09:27,781 --> 00:09:29,515
我没约你而留下永久的伤痛
that was a burn because I wasn't asking you out.

234
00:09:29,516 --> 00:09:31,950
嘿 你是那个我的左脚(电影)
Hey, it's the guy from My Left Foot.

235
00:09:31,951 --> 00:09:35,086
Jonah 你今天跟总统交谈了几次
Jonah, how many times have you talked to the president today?

236
00:09:35,087 --> 00:09:37,221
你想知道吗
Oh, you want to know?

237
00:09:37,222 --> 00:09:40,559
是的 因为你得把它记到冰箱的星形图上去
Yeah, 'cause you need to put it up on that star chart on your refrigerator.

238
00:09:40,560 --> 00:09:42,628
他今天跟我说了四次话 - 四次?
he actually spoke to me four times today. - Four?

239
00:09:42,629 --> 00:09:45,498
简报室 N.S.C.会议 走廊有两次
Briefing room, N.S.C. meeting, hallway twice.

240
00:09:45,499 --> 00:09:47,233
他每次是不是说
And in each of those did he say,

241
00:09:47,234 --> 00:09:49,302
有没有人把这狗娘养的给我赶开?
Someone get this freak the fuck away from me?

242
00:09:49,303 --> 00:09:51,505
嗨 Jonah
Hi, Jonah.

243
00:09:51,506 --> 00:09:53,841
上面有什么新闻
What's the news from the mountaintop?

244
00:09:53,842 --> 00:09:56,945
白宫想... - 等等
The White House would like... - Hang on just a second.

245
00:09:56,946 --> 00:09:58,813
可以帮我记一下吗
Can you do me there?

246
00:09:58,814 --> 00:10:00,748
记着呢 - 继续
Doing you. - What?

247
00:10:00,749 --> 00:10:03,184
白宫想要你替总统出席下午六点的
The White House would like you to atend at 6:00 P.M.

248
00:10:03,185 --> 00:10:05,120
S.R.V.A.募捐活动
S.R.V.A. Fund-raiser tonight instead of the President.

249
00:10:05,121 --> 00:10:06,988
哦 不 我不去 - 日程上没有
- Oh, no, that's not gonna happen. - Not on the schedule.

250
00:10:06,989 --> 00:10:08,530
总统不想回答
The POTUS doesn't want to get hit with questions

251
00:10:08,531 --> 00:10:10,258
那些政府财政账单问题
on the fiscal responsibility bill.

252
00:10:10,259 --> 00:10:11,693
嗯 - 但他们明显不会问你
- Uh-huh. - Obviously they won't ask you guys

253
00:10:11,694 --> 00:10:13,461
因为你没...
because you have no...

254
00:10:13,462 --> 00:10:17,131
呃 你刚分管了其他领域
um, you just have other areas of expertise.

255
00:10:17,132 --> 00:10:20,034
对 清洁工作 也门 火星任务
Yeah, clean jobs, Yemen, mission to Mars.

256
00:10:20,035 --> 00:10:21,903
我不会去 今晚很忙
Yeah, it's not gonna happen. I'm busy tonight.

257
00:10:21,904 --> 00:10:24,739
我们要为清洁工作委员会定位
Yeah, we're positioning ourselves right now with the clean jobs commission.

258
00:10:24,740 --> 00:10:28,176
但是美利坚合众国总统
But the President of the United States of America

259
00:10:28,177 --> 00:10:30,311
很热心地... - 嗯
is very keen... - Uh-huh.

260
00:10:30,312 --> 00:10:31,945
将你的出席列入
That your going to the fund-raiser should be

261
00:10:31,946 --> 00:10:34,448
基本流程
fundamentally the sequence of events

262
00:10:34,449 --> 00:10:36,716
今晚的募捐活动
that does actually take place this evening.

263
00:10:40,755 --> 00:10:43,457
我会打电话
I will make a call.

264
00:10:43,458 --> 00:10:44,970
谢谢
Thank you.

265
00:10:44,971 --> 00:10:47,328
而且我希望你对我说话时注意声调
And I'd like you to watch your tone with me.

266
00:10:47,329 --> 00:10:48,496
我会注意的 - 好
I will watch my tone. - Yeah.

267
00:10:48,497 --> 00:10:50,599
Mike 你也要去 好吧
And, Mike, you need to be there, too, okay?

268
00:10:50,600 --> 00:10:52,267
今晚不能回家遛狗
So no going home to walk your dog.

269
00:10:52,268 --> 00:10:55,271
轮不到你对我说教 见鬼的天才小医生
Uh, don't tell me what to do, Doogie Fucking Howser.

270
00:10:55,272 --> 00:10:57,674
我听不懂你说什么
I don't know what that means.

271
00:10:57,675 --> 00:11:00,342
还有那个左脚什么 - 那电影不错
or your left foot thing. - Great movie.

272
00:11:00,343 --> 00:11:02,978
好 我要回白宫了
Okay, well, I'm going to go back to the White House.

273
00:11:02,979 --> 00:11:05,281
听到这两个字我就硬了
That address makes me hard.

274
00:11:05,282 --> 00:11:07,850
吻你 想你
Kiss you, miss you.

275
00:11:10,687 --> 00:11:13,322
嘿 Mike
Hey, Mike.

276
00:11:13,323 --> 00:11:16,325
你觉得失误是什么
What would you say were the two

277
00:11:16,326 --> 00:11:18,526
在我们竞选中的两大失误
biggest campaign mistakes that we made?

278
00:11:18,527 --> 00:11:20,461
你老是一脸衰相 还有那帽子
You looked tired a lot and the hat.

279
00:11:20,462 --> 00:11:22,419
我喜欢那帽子 你乱说什么
I liked the hat. What are you talking about?

280
00:11:22,420 --> 00:11:24,098
我们因为帽子吃亏了
The hat hurt us.

281
00:11:24,099 --> 00:11:27,668
那帽子让你头型变得很奇怪 就这些
Your head looked weird in the hat, that's all I'm gonna say.

282
00:11:27,669 --> 00:11:29,870
那好...
Okay...

283
00:11:29,871 --> 00:11:31,538
你觉得Dan怎样
What do you think of Dan?

284
00:11:31,539 --> 00:11:34,040
噢 Dan就是坨屎
Oh, Dan is a shit.

285
00:11:34,041 --> 00:11:36,076
你要不要具体一点
You want to expand on that?

286
00:11:36,077 --> 00:11:40,047
可以 他是坨又大又纯的屎
Sure. He's a massive and total shit.

287
00:11:40,048 --> 00:11:42,182
你第一眼看他的时候会想这个人肯定
When you first meet him, you think surely to God

288
00:11:42,183 --> 00:11:45,519
不会像他外表一样衰
this man can't be as big a shit as he seems,

289
00:11:45,520 --> 00:11:47,387
但实际他就是衰
but he is.

290
00:11:47,388 --> 00:11:49,890
其实 我... - 因为 就像这里有本书
- See, I... - 'Cause like if there were a book

291
00:11:49,891 --> 00:11:52,827
封面是屎做的 你会想 真有趣
with covers made of shit, you'd think, That's intriguing.

292
00:11:52,828 --> 00:11:54,929
什么书会让人想到
I wonder what's in this book that they saw fit

293
00:11:54,930 --> 00:11:56,831
用纯屎做封面
to give it covers made of pure shit.

294
00:11:56,832 --> 00:12:00,401
然后你翻开它发现... 是屎
And then you open it and... shit.

295
00:12:03,371 --> 00:12:05,705
非常感谢
Thank you so much. Yes.

296
00:12:05,706 --> 00:12:08,675
你好吗 我看到你了 也看到你了
How are you? I see you. I see you.

297
00:12:08,676 --> 00:12:11,510
Clements参议员在那儿 你得去跟她聊聊
There's congresswoman Clements, you should speak with her.

298
00:12:11,511 --> 00:12:13,713
她有点小胡子 会分散注意
She's got a small mustache. It's a little disturbing.

299
00:12:13,714 --> 00:12:15,281
不要盯着看 知道吗 - 嗯
- Don't stare at it, okay? - Oh. Mm-hmm.

300
00:12:15,282 --> 00:12:17,383
领奖台太高了
The podium is definitely too high.

301
00:12:17,384 --> 00:12:19,752
垫一下 Gary 帮我垫个什么 - 噢 好 好
- Box me, Gary. Box me. - Oh, yeah, yeah.

302
00:12:23,624 --> 00:12:26,860
这里用什么餐具 玉米淀粉的还是塑料的
What is the utensil situation? Is it Cornstarch or plastic here?

303
00:12:26,861 --> 00:12:28,828
离它们远点 餐具有政治意义了
Stay away from both. The utensils are politicized.

304
00:12:28,829 --> 00:12:32,365
你可以拿芹菜铲吃的
You could use celery as a kind of shovel.

305
00:12:32,366 --> 00:12:36,402
你居然跟老板女儿谈恋爱
I cannot believe you are dating your boss's daughter.

306
00:12:36,403 --> 00:12:39,873
她风趣又性感 还能辅助我的事业
She's fun, she's sexy. She can advance my career.

307
00:12:39,874 --> 00:12:41,841
我很喜欢她 - 那才是真相
- I really like her. - That's the one.

308
00:12:41,842 --> 00:12:43,342
她很好 - 那才是真相
- She's great. - That's the one.

309
00:12:43,343 --> 00:12:45,611
我们要探讨下副总统发言内容 好吧
We need to talk about the V.P.'S speech, okay?

310
00:12:45,612 --> 00:12:47,612
什么 - 我能...
What? - Can I just...

311
00:12:47,613 --> 00:12:49,748
别他妈抢我东西 - 谢谢
- Don't grab my shit. - Thank you.

312
00:12:49,749 --> 00:12:52,917
白宫方面说我们要草拟绝大部分 明白吗
White House says we need to majorly redact this, okay?

313
00:12:52,918 --> 00:12:54,418
我来草拟你的驴脸
I'll redact your fucking face.

314
00:12:54,419 --> 00:12:56,187
白宫不希望明天报纸上
The White House does not want anything

315
00:12:56,188 --> 00:12:57,688
出现石油 知道吧
in the papers tomorrow about oil, okay?

316
00:12:57,689 --> 00:12:59,991
什么 - 或者塑料
What? - or plastics.

317
00:12:59,992 --> 00:13:03,294
不能提玉米淀粉 - 她本来就是主管绿色产业的
Nothing about Cornstarch. - Her whole position is green jobs.

318
00:13:03,295 --> 00:13:05,564
又不是我要这样 做就对了
Is doesn't come from me, okay, so just do it.

319
00:13:05,565 --> 00:13:07,566
你乐在其中 乐在其中
You love this. You love this.

320
00:13:07,567 --> 00:13:09,568
我也没想否认没有乐在其中
I'm not gonna say I don't enjoy it.

321
00:13:09,569 --> 00:13:12,405
女士们先生们 今晚
Ladies and gentlemen, I want to welcome you all

322
00:13:12,406 --> 00:13:14,507
我要欢迎并感谢你们的到来
here tonight and thank you for coming.

323
00:13:14,508 --> 00:13:15,942
嗨 Selina - 嘿
- Hi, Selina. - Hey.

324
00:13:15,943 --> 00:13:17,844
演讲只改了一点点 - 改了哪儿
just a small change in The speech. - What is that?

325
00:13:17,845 --> 00:13:20,146
塑料业显然已经找过总统了
Plastics apparently talked to the president.

326
00:13:20,147 --> 00:13:23,382
白宫方面不想我们提到石油 玉米淀粉或者是塑料
The White House doesn't want us mentioning oil or Cornstarch or plastic.

327
00:13:23,383 --> 00:13:25,251
略过就可以了
Just wing it.

328
00:13:25,252 --> 00:13:27,886
全部被铅笔干了一遍吗
This has been pencil-fucked completely?

329
00:13:27,887 --> 00:13:30,656
呃 对 前后夹攻 几乎没前戏
Uh, yes, front and back. Very little romance.

330
00:13:30,657 --> 00:13:32,691
几乎划完了 好吧
That's the entire speech, okay?

331
00:13:32,692 --> 00:13:34,593
这里还剩什么
What's left here? I've got hello

332
00:13:34,594 --> 00:13:36,762
我还有大家好 和... 介词
and I have... Preposions.

333
00:13:36,763 --> 00:13:38,730
你可以谈下你的船
Well, you could talk about your boat.

334
00:13:38,731 --> 00:13:40,232
或者类似的 - 也好 说下那艘船
- Or something like that. - Sure, talk about the boat.

335
00:13:40,233 --> 00:13:42,834
Gary 说真的 你能闭10秒钟嘴吗
Gary, seriously, can you just shut up for 10 seconds?

336
00:13:42,835 --> 00:13:44,669
看不清你在写什么
Okay, now I can't read what you're writing.

337
00:13:44,670 --> 00:13:46,805
放轻松 参议员投票改革是你的强项
Relax, you're really good at Senate vote reform.

338
00:13:46,806 --> 00:13:48,040
说那个 就安全了
Hit that one. That's a home run.

339
00:13:48,041 --> 00:13:49,374
那是你的门面
That's your Sergeant Pepper's.

340
00:13:49,375 --> 00:13:50,776
还可以说高跟鞋笑话
We can also use my kitten heels gag.

341
00:13:50,777 --> 00:13:51,977
行 那个好笑吗 - 不好笑
All right. is that funny? - No.

342
00:13:51,978 --> 00:13:53,212
对他们足够了
It's funny enough for these people.

343
00:13:53,213 --> 00:13:55,481
主要看动词 - 谢谢 我知道了
- Hit the verbs. - Thank you, I've got it.

344
00:13:55,482 --> 00:13:58,350
没事 我做得到 我不...不知道那是什么
It's fine, I can do it. I can't... I don't know what that is.

345
00:13:58,351 --> 00:14:00,486
让我们欢迎副总统Selina Meyer
Please welcome Vice President Selina Meyer.

346
00:14:00,487 --> 00:14:02,455
一举夺钱 - 没多少的
- Go for the money. - It's just pennies.

347
00:14:02,456 --> 00:14:04,223
Hey.

348
00:14:04,224 --> 00:14:06,793
Hi. Oh!

349
00:14:06,794 --> 00:14:10,297
女士们先生们 尊贵的来宾们
Ladies and gentlemen, distinguished guests,

350
00:14:10,298 --> 00:14:12,265
相信你们已经知晓
as I'm sure you're aware,

351
00:14:12,266 --> 00:14:16,237
今晚由我履行总统的职责
I have stepped into the president's shoes this evening,

352
00:14:16,238 --> 00:14:18,205
还有...
and, uh...

353
00:14:18,206 --> 00:14:20,308
谁能想到他还穿矮跟呢
Who knew he wore kitten heels?

354
00:14:23,044 --> 00:14:25,012
当然不穿
Selina: No, he of course doesn't.

355
00:14:25,013 --> 00:14:27,882
他更像是那种穿恨天高的人
He's more of a stilettos kind of guy.

356
00:14:29,919 --> 00:14:32,488
Um...

357
00:14:36,760 --> 00:14:38,194
言归正传
All kidding aside,

358
00:14:38,195 --> 00:14:40,963
今晚有人提醒了我
I am reminded tonight

359
00:14:40,964 --> 00:14:44,466
已故参议员David Reeves
of the late senator David Reeves.

360
00:14:48,137 --> 00:14:50,438
他死了
He died.

361
00:14:50,439 --> 00:14:52,673
他现在死了
He's... he's dead now.

362
00:14:52,674 --> 00:14:55,476
我记得亲爱的David
And I remember dear David

363
00:14:55,477 --> 00:14:58,178
与我和总统谈过
talking to the president and myself

364
00:14:58,179 --> 00:15:00,648
就一项单独的法案
about the absurdity of allowing

365
00:15:00,649 --> 00:15:03,651
进行多重阻挠的荒谬
multiple filibusters on a single bill.

366
00:15:03,652 --> 00:15:06,053
还有...
And...

367
00:15:08,757 --> 00:15:12,660
政治无外乎人民
Politics is about people.

368
00:15:15,031 --> 00:15:16,932
无外乎人民
It's about people.

369
00:15:20,704 --> 00:15:23,939
你们会在推特上谈这些事吗
Uh... - is your guy gonna be tweeting about this?

370
00:15:26,509 --> 00:15:29,211
这么说吧 Sam
Okay, well, let me put it this way, Sam,

371
00:15:29,212 --> 00:15:32,815
那个人已经付不了他的Iphone合约了
that guy is no longer in a position to pay his iPhone contract.

372
00:15:34,685 --> 00:15:38,722
那是因为Mike McClintock 把他扔进了波托马克河
That's because Mike McClintock there threw him into the Potomac River.

373
00:15:41,625 --> 00:15:44,094
天啊 看样子因为那条玉米淀粉推特
Oh, boy. It seems with that Cornstarch tweet,

374
00:15:44,095 --> 00:15:46,529
我们被自己的拖沓给害了
we were hoist by our own retard.

375
00:15:48,765 --> 00:15:51,633
接下来...
Uh, so...

376
00:15:51,634 --> 00:15:53,502
我知道 我知道 我知道我说的是什么
I know. I know. I know what I said.

377
00:15:53,503 --> 00:15:55,637
用了拖沓这个词
It's the use of the word retard.

378
00:15:55,638 --> 00:15:57,439
不是 - 但这是个笑话 是个笑话
- It's just not... - But it was joke. It was joke.

379
00:15:57,440 --> 00:15:58,907
然后世界就安静了
And then everything went silent.

380
00:15:58,908 --> 00:16:01,911
请允许我说句话 我觉得你有必要尽快就此事道歉
If I could, I think it would behoove you to make an apology

381
00:16:01,912 --> 00:16:03,880
我可以给你办公室找一个
as soon as possible, in which case I can get someone in your office

382
00:16:03,881 --> 00:16:06,583
适当的心理健康慈善机构的人...
from an appropriate mental health charity...

383
00:16:06,584 --> 00:16:08,919
这个漂亮的小伙子是谁 这个漂亮的小伙子是谁
Who the fuck is pretty boy? Who the fuck is pretty boy?

384
00:16:08,920 --> 00:16:11,322
明天会上报纸的
Look, it's going to be in the papers tomorrow.

385
00:16:11,323 --> 00:16:14,125
没有必要 没必要大惊小怪的
Not necessarily. Let's not make it the story and panic, okay?

386
00:16:14,126 --> 00:16:16,094
如果Tom Hanks死了呢 - 什么
What if Tom Hanks dies? - What?

387
00:16:16,095 --> 00:16:18,296
想法真阴暗啊 - 我可不希望如此
- What a dark thought. - I'm not wishing that.

388
00:16:18,297 --> 00:16:20,064
我是说什么事都有可能发生 Tom Hanks死了
I'm saying anything could happen... Tom Hanks could die,

389
00:16:20,065 --> 00:16:21,699
在洛杉矶发生森林大火
there could be a forest fire in L.A.

390
00:16:21,700 --> 00:16:24,101
你是怎么得到这份工作的 你真的想把你的公关策略定位在
How did you get this job? You really want to base your press strategy

391
00:16:24,102 --> 00:16:25,903
找出Tom Hanks什么时候会...
based on trying to figure out when Tom Hanks is gonna...

392
00:16:25,904 --> 00:16:28,705
有人是要来搞笑吗 - 看样子是
- Did someone order a dick-o-gram here? - Amy: Yes, seemingly.

393
00:16:28,706 --> 00:16:30,540
我们能不在贮藏室里运筹帷幄吗
Can we not strategize in a closet?

394
00:16:30,541 --> 00:16:33,442
好吧 我们要做的是慢慢走到车里 好吗
All right, what we're gonna do is we're gonna walk slowly to the car, okay?

395
00:16:33,443 --> 00:16:35,611
但你们要围着我 煞有介事
But you guys surround me, very purposeful.

396
00:16:35,612 --> 00:16:37,279
像人肉车队 - 没错
Like a human motorcade. - Exactly.

397
00:16:37,280 --> 00:16:40,482
我们在讨论重要的事情 - 就像教皇
- We're discussing important things. - Like the pope.

398
00:16:40,483 --> 00:16:42,484
拜托 - 走吧
- Come on. - Mike: Let's just roll.

399
00:16:42,485 --> 00:16:45,121
微笑 要微笑 微笑 - 干得好
- And smile, though. Smile, smile. - Wonderful job.

400
00:16:45,122 --> 00:16:48,091
微笑 我们要谈这事
Smiling. And we're gonna talk about that.

401
00:16:48,092 --> 00:16:49,760
不够
It's not enough of a motor...

402
00:16:49,761 --> 00:16:51,996
再来 再来 围住
surround me more, though. Surround it.

403
00:16:51,997 --> 00:16:53,998
围着我 好的 好的
- Surround me. - Okay, I've got it. I've got it.

404
00:16:53,999 --> 00:16:57,401
我得把帘掀起来因为静电会吸引灰尘
I need to keep these off your jacket 'cause the static attracts and retains dirt.

405
00:16:57,402 --> 00:16:59,737
谢谢 Gary 让物理变得有趣起来了
Selina: Thank you, Gary. Making physics fun.

406
00:16:59,738 --> 00:17:03,240
我们每耽误一分钟 拖沓就上升一个字号
Every minute that we delay, Retard goes up a font size.

407
00:17:03,241 --> 00:17:04,708
那开始工作吧
Amy: Well, then start the process.

408
00:17:04,709 --> 00:17:06,843
Mike 我们需要你值夜班
Mike, we're gonna have to have you pull an all-nighter.

409
00:17:06,844 --> 00:17:08,278
不 不行 我养狗了
No, I can't. I've got the dog.

410
00:17:08,279 --> 00:17:10,413
好吧 听着 Mike 你回家
Okay, listen. Mike, you go home.

411
00:17:10,414 --> 00:17:12,915
喂狗 遛狗
Feed the dog. Walk the dog.

412
00:17:12,916 --> 00:17:15,017
开枪把狗打死 埋了它
Shoot the dog. Bury the dog.

413
00:17:15,018 --> 00:17:17,854
然后回来 好吗 - 狗自己能行
- And then come back in, okay? - The dog will be fine.

414
00:17:19,523 --> 00:17:21,758
她一直想表现风趣幽默
She was trying to be funny.

415
00:17:21,759 --> 00:17:24,361
我知道 可她不风趣 我当然知道
I know. She's not funny. Of course I know that.

416
00:17:24,362 --> 00:17:26,997
不 不 不 那个她也没不行 不要
No, no, no. She won't be available for that, either. No.

417
00:17:26,998 --> 00:17:30,334
我不能再拒绝你 我只好...
I can't say no to you again, so I'm just going to...

418
00:17:32,004 --> 00:17:33,505
早晨好
Good morning.

419
00:17:33,506 --> 00:17:35,974
看过这个吗
Seen this?

420
00:17:37,243 --> 00:17:40,145
所有人都看过了吗 好好看过了吗
Everybody seen it? Everybody got a good look?

421
00:17:40,146 --> 00:17:43,348
华盛顿邮报时尚版的头版
Front page of the style section of the Washington Post.

422
00:17:43,349 --> 00:17:46,150
你是首席联络官 对吗
You're the head of communications, is that correct?

423
00:17:46,151 --> 00:17:48,185
是的 女士 - 把衬衣塞进去
- Yes, ma'am. - Tuck your shirt in.

424
00:17:48,186 --> 00:17:50,687
好吗 你的老二在裤子外边晃悠
Okay? Your dick is hanging out of your pants.

425
00:17:52,089 --> 00:17:53,823
Sue 总统打电话来了吗
Sue, did the president call?

426
00:17:53,824 --> 00:17:55,858
没有 - 没有
No. - No.

427
00:17:58,895 --> 00:18:01,330
嘿 大家好 - 天啊
- Hey, everyone. - Oh, God.

428
00:18:01,331 --> 00:18:05,467
今天早晨要应付什么烂摊子
Hey, what colossal fuckup are we dealing with this morning?

429
00:18:05,468 --> 00:18:08,737
副总统把最后的雪豹干死了吗
Did the VEEP kill the last remaining snow leopard?

430
00:18:08,738 --> 00:18:11,139
她用燃烧弹炸收容所了吗
Did she firebomb a hospice?

431
00:18:11,140 --> 00:18:13,008
我没时间无视你 Jonah
I don't have time to ignore you, Jonah.

432
00:18:13,009 --> 00:18:15,076
Gary 帮我无视Jonah好吗
Gary, could you please ignore Jonah for me?

433
00:18:15,077 --> 00:18:17,412
你想怎么样 Jonah - 我有一张慰问卡
- What do you want, Jonah? - I have a condolence card

434
00:18:17,413 --> 00:18:18,846
给Reeves参议员的遗孀
for senator Reeves' widow.

435
00:18:18,847 --> 00:18:21,349
总统签了 需要副总统签字
POTUS has signed, the VPOTUS needs to sign.

436
00:18:21,350 --> 00:18:23,351
然后我要把这个带到国会山
And then I'm gonna take this to the Hill, okay?

437
00:18:23,352 --> 00:18:26,187
你说得好像是递交人权法案
You talk as if you're passing the civil rights act.

438
00:18:26,188 --> 00:18:29,190
注意 - 帅哥 做什么呢
- Look alive, gang. - Hey, good-looking. What you got cooking?

439
00:18:29,191 --> 00:18:31,259
老二派?
Dickwad pie?

440
00:18:31,260 --> 00:18:33,294
Amy 这位是Paul Burton
Amy, this is Paul Burton. He's the chair

441
00:18:33,295 --> 00:18:35,396
他是成人智障患者基金会的主席
of the American Foundation for Adult Mental Disabilities.

442
00:18:35,397 --> 00:18:37,798
你好 - 很高兴见到你 我是Amy
- Hi. How are you? - Hi. It's nice to meet you. I'm Amy.

443
00:18:37,799 --> 00:18:39,634
Burton先生 很高兴你能来我的办公室
Mr. Burton, love to bring you into my office.

444
00:18:39,635 --> 00:18:42,637
谢谢 - 你知道我有自己的旗吗
Thank you. - Did you know that I have my own flag?

445
00:18:42,638 --> 00:18:46,274
女士 有一张给Reeves参议员遗孀的慰问卡
Ma'am, I have a condolence card here for senator Reeves' widow.

446
00:18:46,275 --> 00:18:49,044
Amy 你能...
Oh, Amy, can you...

447
00:18:49,045 --> 00:18:52,247
Gary 两杯咖啡 - 好的
- Gary, we are going to need two coffees. - Okay.

448
00:18:52,248 --> 00:18:54,716
不应该是三杯吗 - 两杯就行了
- Shouldn't that be three? - Two is good.

449
00:18:56,852 --> 00:18:58,854
伙计们 有个男人死了
Uh, guys, a man is dead.

450
00:18:58,855 --> 00:19:02,323
如果一个性骚扰犯死了 我们给他妻子一张签了名的卡片
When a sexual harasser dies, we sign his wife's card.

451
00:19:02,324 --> 00:19:04,359
华盛顿风格一向如此
Okay? That's how Washington works.

452
00:19:04,360 --> 00:19:06,728
我来签 - 好 谢谢
- I will sign it. - Fine, thank you.

453
00:19:06,729 --> 00:19:09,464
她教我这么签她名字的
That was her telling me to sign her name.

454
00:19:09,465 --> 00:19:11,733
如果她想签你的名字 她会这样
If she'd wanted me to sign your name, she would have done this...

455
00:19:13,936 --> 00:19:15,870
我不懂
That didn't get me.

456
00:19:15,871 --> 00:19:17,639
我是说 我错误判断了一些事
Selina: I mean, I misjudged things.

457
00:19:17,640 --> 00:19:20,107
起码我会说我开错了玩笑
Fundamentally, I would say I misjoked.

458
00:19:20,108 --> 00:19:21,876
我是说 如果我们真的要...
I mean, if we were gonna really be...

459
00:19:21,877 --> 00:19:24,312
腹黑高鸟人
Ha-ha! Tall, dark and tiresome,

460
00:19:24,313 --> 00:19:26,581
你得滚回到老板脚下去了
you need to get back to your boss's corner.

461
00:19:26,582 --> 00:19:28,750
Hallowes也中枪了 有博客爆料称
Hallowes is on the ropes. She was reported by the blog

462
00:19:28,751 --> 00:19:32,153
已故参议员Reeves和她有过一段不伦性史
saying that the late senator Reeves had a history of sexual misconduct.

463
00:19:32,154 --> 00:19:35,122
知道吗 我不为Hallowes参议员工作了
Yeah, well, you know what? I don't work for senator Hallowes.

464
00:19:35,123 --> 00:19:36,824
我一个小时前辞职的
I resigned just about an hour ago.

465
00:19:36,825 --> 00:19:40,327
开什么玩笑 - 就在我泄密了那个故事以后
- Are you kidding me? - Yeah, right after I leaked that story.

466
00:19:40,328 --> 00:19:42,296
你在谋划什么 - 什么
What are you planning? - What?

467
00:19:42,297 --> 00:19:43,998
什么 - 什么
What? - What?

468
00:19:43,999 --> 00:19:47,102
你能盯着他吗
Can you please keep your eye on him, please?

469
00:19:47,103 --> 00:19:49,772
因为这太扯淡了 - 好的
- 'Cause this is shady shit. - Okay.

470
00:19:49,773 --> 00:19:52,374
好的 Mike 我们这么做
All right, Mike, here's what we do, okay?

471
00:19:52,375 --> 00:19:54,744
11点半的时候 你说Hallowes参议员
At the 11:30, you say that senator Hallowes

472
00:19:54,745 --> 00:19:56,412
不仅污辱了已故参议员Reeves
not only insulted the late senator Reeves,

473
00:19:56,413 --> 00:19:58,281
而且她煽动
but that she also encouraged...

474
00:19:58,282 --> 00:20:00,817
不 等等 要加重语气 她鼓励
no, wait, strike that... she goaded

475
00:20:00,818 --> 00:20:03,653
副总统在笑话中用拖沓这个词
the V.P. into using the word retard in a joke.

476
00:20:03,654 --> 00:20:05,955
知道我在做什么了吗 Halowes参议员
See what I'm doing? Senator Hallowes

477
00:20:05,956 --> 00:20:07,956
要为拖沓门负责
is responsible for retardgate.

478
00:20:07,957 --> 00:20:10,392
你是那种故作聪明的人吗
Are you like a guy trying to be clever?

479
00:20:10,393 --> 00:20:12,528
因为看起来像
'Cause you seem like a guy who thinks he's being clever.

480
00:20:12,529 --> 00:20:15,564
好好看看我
Take a good look at me okay?

481
00:20:15,565 --> 00:20:17,666
问问你自己 Mike
Now ask yourself something, Mike.

482
00:20:17,667 --> 00:20:19,000
你眼前的这个人
Is the man you're looking at

483
00:20:19,001 --> 00:20:21,303
在未来的一年内会
gonna be in a position a year from now

484
00:20:21,304 --> 00:20:23,139
当你的老板还是手下?
working above you or below you?

485
00:20:23,140 --> 00:20:25,408
很多年前你有的是踌躇满志
'Cause all ambition you had left your body a long time ago

486
00:20:25,409 --> 00:20:28,411
在未来10年的工作生涯中 你所有的只是
and now all you've got left in the last 10 remaining years of your working life

487
00:20:28,412 --> 00:20:30,480
潮湿的公寓 冰冷的蟹饼
is a damp apartment, cold crab cakes,

488
00:20:30,481 --> 00:20:32,049
还有一只隐形的狗
and an invisible fucking dog.

489
00:20:32,050 --> 00:20:34,051
你到底想不想照这个计划执行
Do you want to follow this plan or not?

490
00:20:34,052 --> 00:20:36,020
好好算算 哥们
Make a calculation, buddy.

491
00:20:36,021 --> 00:20:37,655
Um...

492
00:20:37,656 --> 00:20:41,826
你获得工科学士学位的时候 没学过怎么写新闻报道吗
In your poly-sci B.A., did you ever learn how to write a press release?

493
00:20:41,827 --> 00:20:43,027
我想我听说过
I think I might have heard of that.

494
00:20:43,028 --> 00:20:44,228
我会教你 - 好的
Let me teach you. - Okay.

495
00:20:44,229 --> 00:20:46,263
Jonah走了吗
Did Jonah leave?

496
00:20:46,264 --> 00:20:48,565
他拿着慰问卡走了吗
Is he gone with that condolence card?

497
00:20:48,566 --> 00:20:49,833
是 他刚走
Yeah, he just left.

498
00:20:49,834 --> 00:20:54,303
我想我签了我的名字
'Cause I think that I signed my name.

499
00:20:54,304 --> 00:20:56,739
什么 - 不是Selina的名字 我的名字
- What? - Not Selina's name, my name.

500
00:20:56,740 --> 00:20:58,341
好吧 好吧 等等
Okay, whoa, whoa. Okay, wait.

501
00:20:58,342 --> 00:21:01,577
从1到10的肯定程度依次增加 你有多肯定
How sure are you on a scale of one to 10? Like one is the...

502
00:21:01,578 --> 00:21:03,647
我知道这范围什么意思 Gary
Yeah, yeah, I can work out how the fucking scale will go, Gary.

503
00:21:03,648 --> 00:21:05,849
呃...9 - 那就差不多是10了
- Uh, nine. - That's almost a full 10.

504
00:21:05,850 --> 00:21:08,285
是 我签了我名字 - 父亲啊
- Yeah, I signed my name. - Oh, father.

505
00:21:08,286 --> 00:21:10,687
看上去好像副总统根本不屑
It's gonna look like the VEEP couldn't be bothered to sign

506
00:21:10,688 --> 00:21:13,690
给国会最受尊重的变态签慰问卡一样
a condolence card for one of the most respected perverts in the Senate.

507
00:21:13,691 --> 00:21:15,425
如果我在写回忆录 其实没写
If I were writing a memoir, which I'm not,

508
00:21:15,426 --> 00:21:19,163
但如果我写 这可是个大时刻
but if I were, whew, this would be a big moment.

509
00:21:19,164 --> 00:21:20,965
不能让人知道
No one can know about this.

510
00:21:20,966 --> 00:21:22,767
不能让她知道
- She cannot know about this. - Sue: Duh.

511
00:21:22,768 --> 00:21:27,071
不 不 Gary Gary 你在做什么
- No, no, no, Gary! - Gary, what are you doing?

512
00:21:27,072 --> 00:21:30,575
真的很抱歉 我要和你说点事
Gary: So sorry. I just need to tell you somethg.

513
00:21:41,521 --> 00:21:44,489
搞毛啊 Amy
What the fuck, Amy?

514
00:21:47,393 --> 00:21:51,163
我在里面想把两把火灭了
I am putting out two fires in there,

515
00:21:51,164 --> 00:21:54,833
然后转过头发现
and I turn around to find out that you have set fire

516
00:21:54,834 --> 00:21:56,602
你把消防车点着了
to the fucking fire truck.

517
00:21:56,603 --> 00:21:58,404
抱歉 抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry, sorry.

518
00:21:58,405 --> 00:22:02,475
这个办公室里人员的不称职程度 简直到了天理不容的地步
The level of incompetence in this office is staggering.

519
00:22:02,476 --> 00:22:04,643
我们会把卡拿回来
We are going to get the card back

520
00:22:04,644 --> 00:22:06,178
换张新的
and replace it with a new one.

521
00:22:06,179 --> 00:22:08,113
对 没错 - 很简单的
- Yeah, that's right. - Simple.

522
00:22:08,114 --> 00:22:09,676
你去办
You're gonna get on it.

523
00:22:09,677 --> 00:22:12,484
把这个搞定 好吗
You are going to shut this the fuck down, okay?

524
00:22:12,485 --> 00:22:17,123
因为我忙着跟倒霉的拖沓
Because I am busy in there apologizing to that...

525
00:22:17,124 --> 00:22:18,858
道歉
Fucktard.

526
00:22:21,996 --> 00:22:23,330
天啊
God!

527
00:22:23,331 --> 00:22:26,233
好吧
Okay. It's fine.

528
00:22:28,136 --> 00:22:30,837
Burton先生 我很抱歉
Mr. Burton. I am so sorry.

529
00:22:30,838 --> 00:22:32,873
今天真是状况百出
We're having a complicated day here.

530
00:22:34,910 --> 00:22:37,178
我不太想开这个新闻发布会
I'm not happy about having to give this press briefing.

531
00:22:37,179 --> 00:22:39,614
当然 您的幸福与否是我的首要任务
Yeah, and of course your happiness is top of my agenda,

532
00:22:39,615 --> 00:22:41,649
远远高于气候问题和买卖儿童
right above climate control and child trafficking.

533
00:22:41,650 --> 00:22:43,885
天啊 会不会发展成狗血情节
Oh, my gosh, is this gonna become like Moonlighting

534
00:22:43,886 --> 00:22:45,520
我们坠入爱河然后开始乱搞
where we fall in love and start fucking?

535
00:22:45,521 --> 00:22:49,524
Gary要去Jonah的办公室
Amy: Gary is going to go to Jonah's office

536
00:22:49,525 --> 00:22:53,729
然后神不知鬼不觉地把卡拿回来
and somewhat surreptitiously get the card back.

537
00:22:53,730 --> 00:22:55,431
我没穿大衣 我得把卡藏起来
Well, I don't have a coat. I need to hide the card.

538
00:22:55,432 --> 00:22:57,099
我大衣上有咖啡
There's coffee on my coat.

539
00:22:57,100 --> 00:22:58,767
你可以借我的大衣
Sue: You can borrow my coat.

540
00:22:58,768 --> 00:23:00,702
谢谢 Sue 谢谢 Sue
Thank you, Sue. Thank you, Sue.

541
00:23:00,703 --> 00:23:02,237
谢谢 Sue - 解决办法 Sue
- Thanks, Sue. - Solution, Sue.

542
00:23:02,238 --> 00:23:05,073
当然有解决办法 - 谢谢
- Of course. There's some solutions. - Thank you.

543
00:23:06,976 --> 00:23:11,112
谢谢 你真好
Thank you so much. That was really kind of you.

544
00:23:11,113 --> 00:23:13,981
首先你要把帽子摘了
First of all, you should put the hood down.

545
00:23:13,982 --> 00:23:16,350
我没打算把帽子戴上
I wasn't going to put the hood up.

546
00:23:16,351 --> 00:23:18,219
祝你好运 Gary
Well, good luck, Gary.

547
00:23:18,220 --> 00:23:21,088
我相信你还是能干好的
I am convinced that you can probably do this.

548
00:23:21,089 --> 00:23:22,624
谢谢
Thank you.

549
00:23:22,625 --> 00:23:25,259
用我通知他们你要来吗
Sue: Want me to ring through, tell them you're coming?

550
00:23:25,260 --> 00:23:27,662
不 天啊 - 好吧 一个笑话
- No, my God! - Okay, okay, a joke.

551
00:23:27,663 --> 00:23:30,365
点燃了现场的情绪
Hello. Lightening the mood here.

552
00:23:30,366 --> 00:23:33,735
天啊 -  Amy 想个B计划吧
- Oh, my God. - Amy, come up with a plan B.

553
00:23:33,736 --> 00:23:35,204
好吧 因为...
Okay? 'Cause...

554
00:23:51,887 --> 00:23:53,988
Gary?

555
00:23:57,425 --> 00:23:58,792
Jonah.

556
00:23:58,793 --> 00:24:00,728
你是来偷那张错签的卡吗
Are you here to steal the incorrectly-signed card?

557
00:24:00,729 --> 00:24:04,032
拜托 不是 - 这场面看上去真的很糟
- Come on, no. - This looks really bad.

558
00:24:04,033 --> 00:24:06,535
不糟 - Gary 我是你朋友
- It's not bad. - Gary, I'm a friend of yours.

559
00:24:06,536 --> 00:24:09,338
我觉得你不是
I don't think you are.

560
00:24:09,339 --> 00:24:10,940
根本不是 - 我开玩笑呢
- At all. - I'm just kidding.

561
00:24:10,941 --> 00:24:14,310
Gary 放松好吗 我会把卡给你
Gary, loosen up, okay? I'm gonna give you the card, all right?

562
00:24:14,311 --> 00:24:16,980
好吗 说实话 我有点害怕
Alright. To be honest, I was a little scared.

563
00:24:16,981 --> 00:24:18,548
是啊 是啊
Yeah, yeah.

564
00:24:18,549 --> 00:24:20,951
给你 - 谢谢
There It is. - Thank you.

565
00:24:20,952 --> 00:24:22,486
只是真的 - 好吧
- It's just really... - Okay.

566
00:24:22,487 --> 00:24:25,022
抱歉 - 说条件吧
- I'm sorry. - Let's just get to the bad part.

567
00:24:25,023 --> 00:24:27,024
说吧 因为我知道你有条件
Let's just get to the bad part 'cause I know you got one.

568
00:24:27,025 --> 00:24:29,860
我不喜欢这种紧张气氛
I don't like tension. I got acid reflux. Let's get to the bad part.

569
00:24:29,861 --> 00:24:32,529
我想今晚和Amy约会
I want Amy to go on a date with me tonight.

570
00:24:32,530 --> 00:24:35,733
好吧 好吧 好吧 这不可能
Okay, okay, okay. That's impossible.

571
00:24:35,734 --> 00:24:37,802
别担心 好吗 我们不会上床
Don't worry about it, okay? We're not gonna have sex, all right?

572
00:24:37,803 --> 00:24:39,704
因为她恨我 - 好吧
Because She hates me. - Okay. Uh-huh.

573
00:24:39,705 --> 00:24:42,507
但Amy是个8分 - 好吧
- But Amy's an eight. - Okay.

574
00:24:42,508 --> 00:24:45,343
如果所有我想与之发生关系的8分
And if all the other eights that I do want to have sex with

575
00:24:45,344 --> 00:24:47,245
知道我能把到一个8分
see that I am eight-capable,

576
00:24:47,246 --> 00:24:50,382
那我很快就能和一个8分上床了
then I'm going to be having sex with an eight very soon.

577
00:24:50,383 --> 00:24:51,750
这是实习季 Gary
It is intern season, Gary.

578
00:24:51,751 --> 00:24:54,053
你看我像拉皮条的吗
Do I look like a pimp to you?

579
00:24:54,054 --> 00:24:57,356
你看起来就是个拉皮条的
You look exactly like a pimp.

580
00:24:58,792 --> 00:25:01,494
Dan 等着掉馅饼呢
Dan, waiting for some crumbs to fall?

581
00:25:01,495 --> 00:25:03,129
去死 - 不
- Fuck off. - Sue: Uh, no.

582
00:25:03,130 --> 00:25:04,731
我得和她谈一下
Got to talk to her for one moment, please.

583
00:25:04,732 --> 00:25:06,933
她现在真的很忙
No, she's actually really burdened right now with a bunch of...

584
00:25:06,934 --> 00:25:09,235
真的 一秒钟的事
Sue, it'll take one second, literally.

585
00:25:09,236 --> 00:25:12,338
Mike 她在转圈呢 - 好吧 我再来
- Mike, she's spinning. - Oh, okay. I'll come back.

586
00:25:18,445 --> 00:25:20,579
嘿 小南瓜 什么事
Hey, what's up, pumpkin?

587
00:25:20,580 --> 00:25:22,615
你怎么还在这儿
What the fuck are you still doing here?

588
00:25:22,616 --> 00:25:24,684
副总统让我来的
Vice President asked me to stop by.

589
00:25:24,685 --> 00:25:26,419
好吧
Right.

590
00:25:26,420 --> 00:25:29,122
加油 Gary 加油 加油 Gary
Go, Gary. Go, go, go, Gary.

591
00:25:29,123 --> 00:25:31,992
加油 Gary - 干得好
- Go, Gary. - Well done, buddy.

592
00:25:31,993 --> 00:25:33,760
不 你 - 是的
- No, you didn't. - Yes.

593
00:25:33,761 --> 00:25:35,295
拿到了 - 是的
- You got it? - Yes, I did.

594
00:25:35,296 --> 00:25:38,031
哇 Gary 你干得好
Wow, Gary. Good for you.

595
00:25:38,032 --> 00:25:39,899
很好 抱歉
Good for... oh. Excuse me.

596
00:25:39,900 --> 00:25:41,468
嘿 很好
Hey, all right.

597
00:25:41,469 --> 00:25:43,570
是的 虽然我和Jonah做了交易
Yeah, although I did have to make a deal with Jonah.

598
00:25:43,571 --> 00:25:46,073
Amy今晚要和他约会
Amy's got to go on a date with him tonight.

599
00:25:46,074 --> 00:25:48,342
不 不行
Oh, no, she's not.

600
00:25:48,343 --> 00:25:50,110
他不想和你上床
Well, he doesn't want to have sex with you.

601
00:25:50,111 --> 00:25:51,579
只想晚饭和电影
He just wants dinner and a movie.

602
00:25:51,580 --> 00:25:54,115
不 Amy不会和Jonah约会的
No, Amy is not going on a date with Jonah.

603
00:25:54,116 --> 00:25:57,851
镇静 不上床的约会
Get a grip. It's a date and no sex.

604
00:25:57,852 --> 00:26:00,287
对我来讲 这是12年的婚姻
For me, that was 12 years of marriage.

605
00:26:00,288 --> 00:26:03,223
我给你们找个旅馆
- I'll get you guys a motel. - Ugh.

606
00:26:03,224 --> 00:26:05,126
天啊 不
Selina: Oh, God, no!

607
00:26:05,127 --> 00:26:07,595
闪开 闪开 闪开
Make a hole! Make a hole! Make a hole!

608
00:26:07,596 --> 00:26:09,229
天啊 - 看看这个
- Oh, my God. - Look at this.

609
00:26:09,230 --> 00:26:10,598
什么 什么 - 看
What? What? - Look.

610
00:26:10,599 --> 00:26:13,167
总统已经签了这个
The President already signed this one.

611
00:26:13,168 --> 00:26:17,371
我们得在新的上伪造总统的签名
Okay? We're gonna have to forge the President's signature on the new one.

612
00:26:17,372 --> 00:26:18,973
这可是死刑
Gary: Well, that's a capital offense.

613
00:26:18,974 --> 00:26:22,142
告诉你们 这可是会被电椅处决的
Yeah, you could be legally electrocuted for doing that, just so you know.

614
00:26:22,143 --> 00:26:24,445
我没在 我很明确地拒绝了
I'm not here. I have plausible deniability.

615
00:26:24,446 --> 00:26:26,012
听着 我来 我做
Dan: Look, I'll do it. I got it.

616
00:26:26,013 --> 00:26:29,115
关键是上下颠倒了
The key is you do it upside down.

617
00:26:31,018 --> 00:26:32,685
太夸张了
That is extraordinary.

618
00:26:32,686 --> 00:26:34,386
有你不能做的吗
Is there anything you can't do?

619
00:26:34,387 --> 00:26:36,722
前戏 阳光直射
Amy: Foreplay, direct sunlight.

620
00:26:36,723 --> 00:26:39,825
女士 我任您差遣 - Amy 是的
- Ma'am, I am at your service. - Um, Amy, yes.

621
00:26:39,826 --> 00:26:42,394
我想和你谈谈这事
I wanted to talk to you about this.

622
00:26:42,395 --> 00:26:45,097
我给Dan提供了一份永久职位
I have offered Dan a permanent post

623
00:26:45,098 --> 00:26:46,999
在这个办公室 好的
Here in The office. - Okay.

624
00:26:47,000 --> 00:26:48,901
很好 - 没问题
Great. - Not a problem.

625
00:26:48,902 --> 00:26:50,637
我去给黑莓充电
I'll get the BlackBerry fired up.

626
00:26:50,638 --> 00:26:53,139
我没问题 - 好的
Sounds good to me. - Here We go.

627
00:26:53,140 --> 00:26:55,643
有时间吗 - 有
do you have a second? - Sure.

628
00:26:57,612 --> 00:26:59,614
你雇他了 - 嗯
you hired him? - Mm-hmm.

629
00:26:59,615 --> 00:27:00,948
你雇了华盛顿头号混蛋
You hired the biggest bastard in D.C.?

630
00:27:00,949 --> 00:27:02,951
是的 我擅长和混蛋打交道
Oh, yeah, well, I'm fluent in bastard.

631
00:27:02,952 --> 00:27:04,419
是我的招牌之一
Okay? It's one of my languages.

632
00:27:04,420 --> 00:27:06,956
Amy 我利用Dan得到我想要的东西
Amy, I used Dan to get what I wanted.

633
00:27:06,957 --> 00:27:09,592
他利用你得到他想要的
He used you to get what he wanted.

634
00:27:09,593 --> 00:27:12,495
不 我肯定是利用他
Uh-uh, no. I definitely used him.

635
00:27:12,496 --> 00:27:14,764
我是利用者 他是被用者
I'm the user, and he's the usee.

636
00:27:14,765 --> 00:27:17,567
好吧 Amy 来了
Okay, Amy, here we go.

637
00:27:17,568 --> 00:27:19,436
虾仁意面再来一个A片
Shrimp Linguini and a porno.

638
00:27:19,437 --> 00:27:21,137
嘿 开玩笑
Oh, hey. I'm just kidding.

639
00:27:21,138 --> 00:27:23,106
是鸡肉意面 我马上到
It's chicken Linguini. I'll be over here.

640
00:27:23,107 --> 00:27:26,343
Dan是个阴谋家 他很狡猾
Dan is manipulative. He is cunning.

641
00:27:26,344 --> 00:27:29,346
我知道 所以我才会雇他 你为什么不听我的
I know. That's why I hired him. Why aren't you listening to me?

642
00:27:29,347 --> 00:27:32,649
半年内 所有这些烂事消停了
In six months, when all this bullshit dies down,

643
00:27:32,650 --> 00:27:35,318
我们往清洁工作委员会里安插一个石油的人
we're gonna put an oil guy on the clean jobs commission.

644
00:27:35,319 --> 00:27:37,486
你要往清洁工作上泼石油
You're pouring oil on clean jobs?

645
00:27:37,487 --> 00:27:39,856
天啊 Amy 成熟点吧
Oh, please, please, Amy, grow up.

646
00:27:39,857 --> 00:27:42,326
他们就是这样解决古巴导弹问题的
This is how they solved the Cuban missile crisis.

647
00:27:42,327 --> 00:27:43,827
这是我的古巴
This is my Cuba.

648
00:27:43,828 --> 00:27:46,330
Dan告诉你这是你的古巴吗
Did Dan tell you that this is your Cuba?

649
00:27:46,331 --> 00:27:47,866
他真是坨屎
He's such a shit.

650
00:27:47,867 --> 00:27:49,434
我知道 我就是想告诉你这个
I know, that's what I'm trying to tell you.

651
00:27:49,435 --> 00:27:52,972
你就是把他当坨屎卖给我的 所以我雇了他
You sold him to me as a shit and that's why I hired him.

652
00:27:52,973 --> 00:27:55,674
他恶心屎我了 我需要这坨屎
He's shitty me, okay? I need a shit.

653
00:27:55,675 --> 00:28:00,078
你一定会后悔 - Amy 我需要屎
- You are so going to regret... - Amy, I need a shit.

654
00:28:00,079 --> 00:28:02,480
有人吗 你好 - 你好
- Knock, knock. Hello. - Hello.

655
00:28:02,481 --> 00:28:05,817
塑料和纤维素化合物协会的Bob Jeffries
Bob Jeffries of the Plastics and Cellulose Association.

656
00:28:05,818 --> 00:28:07,318
副总统 - 你好
Madam Vice President. - How do you do?

657
00:28:07,319 --> 00:28:09,020
请进 - 非常感谢
- Please, come into my office. - Thank you so much.

658
00:28:09,021 --> 00:28:10,822
你知道我有自己的旗吗
Do you know that I have my own flag?

659
00:28:10,823 --> 00:28:13,724
希望是我们的纤维素化合物做的旗
Well, I hope that's one of our cellulose flags.

660
00:28:13,725 --> 00:28:15,859
你太过了
Oh, you're too much.

661
00:28:23,501 --> 00:28:25,836
你的战车在等
Jonah: Your chariot awaits.

662
00:28:25,837 --> 00:28:28,405
所以 拿上你的大衣
So, yeah, grab your coat.

663
00:28:28,406 --> 00:28:32,309
小Jack Horner 你在这儿啊
Okay, little Jack Horner, there you are.

664
00:28:32,310 --> 00:28:34,145
全新的办公桌在等着你
You got a brand-new desk in the corner.

665
00:28:34,146 --> 00:28:35,846
跟着我 我已经给你找一个绝佳的摆放位置
Follow me, I've got a beautiful spot

666
00:28:35,847 --> 00:28:38,649
为你女朋友Carol Hallowes的可爱的照片
for your adoring photo of girlfriend Carol Hallowes.

667
00:28:38,650 --> 00:28:40,384
事实上 她不再是我女朋友了
Actually, she's not my girlfriend anymore.

668
00:28:40,385 --> 00:28:42,719
我15分钟以前用短信跟她分手了
I just broke up with her about 15 minutes ago via text.

669
00:28:42,720 --> 00:28:45,656
冷酷无情啊 - 其实是个应用程序
- Well, cold and rather nerdy. - Actually, it was an app.

670
00:28:45,657 --> 00:28:47,858
好吧 搬走 滑头要搬进来
All right, move out. Slick's moving in.

671
00:28:47,859 --> 00:28:51,195
Gary 能拿两杯咖啡来吗？
Selina: Gary, can we get two coffees in here?

672
00:28:51,196 --> 00:28:53,697
不要甜味剂
No sweeteners.

673
00:28:53,698 --> 00:28:56,183
不要甜味剂 - 糖
Gary: No sweeteners? - Sugar.

674
00:28:56,184 --> 00:28:58,568
不要甜味剂? - 不要甜味剂 糖
No sweeteners? - No sweeteners. Sugar.

675
00:29:02,280 --> 00:29:03,925
敢碰我 你的一根手指就别要了
Touch me and you lose a finger.

676
00:29:04,652 --> 00:29:05,652
还有你的一个蛋蛋
And a ball.

